Guide to the Frederick Herzog Papers, 1947-2011 and undated (bulk 1947-1995) RL.00536
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Frederick Herzog papers
1947-2011 (bulk 1947-1995)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Herzog, Frederick
RL.00536
32.4 Linear Feet
Frederick Herzog (1925-1995), former faculty member at the Duke Divinity School, was well known for his work on civil rights and liberation theology. The collection provides rich documentary evidence on the historical connections between religion, the Civil Rights Movement, and human rights. Material includes audio cassettes of lectures, minutes from Herzog's lectures and classes, several English and German manuscripts of Herzog's publications, research files, photographs, significant correspondence, and speeches and lectures. Several materials dated after 1995 were contributed by Kristin Herzog, Frederick Herzog's wife.
24,300 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Frederick Herzog Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift beginning in 2007.
Biographical Note
A native of North Dakota, Frederick Herzog earned his doctorate from Princeton University after having studied in Germany and Switzerland, where he was an assistant to professor Karl Barth. In 1960, he joined the faculty at Duke Divinity School. Herzog taught religion at Duke until his sudden death during a faculty meeting in 1995. In the spring of 1970 he wrote the first North American article on liberation theology, and in 1972 his Liberation Theology was published. In Justice Church Herzog extended his methodology for liberation theology in North America. While his theology grew directly out of the Civil Rights struggle of the US South, not out of Latin America, his writings in the last 8 years of his life were strongly affected by his experiences in Latin America, especially in Peru. An article by Herzog, "New Spirituality as Grassroots of New Doctrine," was published posthumously in On the Way: The Teaching Church, edited by Frederick Trost.
Herzog's books include: Liberation Theology, Understanding God, God Walk,and Justice Church. Four books have been published referring to his work: Theology and Corporate Conscience: Essays in Honor of Frederick Herzog, edited by M.D. Meeks, J. Moltmann, F.R. Trost, Theology from the Belly of the Whale: A Frederick Herzog Reader and Liberating the Future: God, Mammon, and Theology, both edited by Jörg Rieger, and Remember the Poor: The Challenge to Theology in the Twenty-First Century, by Jörg Rieger. In addition, an article about Herzog titled "In Gratitude for Frederick Herzog" can be found in Frederick Trost's We Know Only in Part: Reflections on a Journey in Faith.
Collection Overview
The Frederick Herzog Papers span the years 1947-2011 with the bulk of the material spanning the years 1947-1995, the year of Herzog's death. These papers provide rich documentary evidence on the historical connections between religion, the Civil Rights Movement, and human rights. The material covers specific areas in which Herzog was involved such as the Civil Rights Movement in Durham and other parts of North Carolina, Durham and Duke University history, student unrest in the 1960s, and human rights issues in Peru in the late 1980s and early 1990s. The collection includes video and audiocassettes regarding Herzog's involvement in Peru and various lectures and classes on theology. His work as a professor at the Duke Divinity School and with various other theological and civil rights organizations is documented in the correspondence he sent to and received from various individuals and groups, as well as in the various committee documents and minutes that record his professional activity in the university. The bulk of material on courses taught and lectures given by Herzog, as well as his participation in both the student exchange program with the University of Bonn and in the Peru and Bolivia student exchange program, can be found in his notebooks and course materials. A large part of this collection is comprised of Herzog's research files on religion, civil rights, labor organizing, racial issues, and protest in North Carolina and nationally, including Herzog's own participation in civil disobedience. Noteable research projects include his work in Peru, his work with the United Church of Christ (UCC) and the Evangelical Church of the Union (EKU), and his work with black churches and theology. This collection also contains original annotated drafts of a variety of Herzog's publications, sermons, speeches and lectures.
Arrangement note
The Audiovisual Series contains two LP records, photographs, a reel of a debate panel and a reel of an interview, as well as audiotapes of several of Herzog's class sessions and VHS tapes regarding churches in Peru.
The Biographical Series contains various articles and items relating to Herzog's death and other miscellaneous biographical information.
The Correspondence Series contains letters in English and German written to and received from Frederick Herzog. Significant correspondents include Brevard S. Childs, J.L. Mays, Eberhard Jüngel, Ernst Käsemann, Jürgen Moltmann, Gustavo Gutiérrez and James Cone, as well as correspondence regarding Peru.
The Course Materials Series contains material related to Herzog's theology and philosophy courses, as well as material on the Duke student exchange program with the University of Bonn, Germany.
The Notebooks Series contains notebooks of Herzog's lectures and student-kept logs of class sessions. These are arranged chronologically.
The Research Files Series contains Frederick Herzog's research files on religion, civil rights, labor organizing, North Carolina, Peru, and other topics. The series includes newspaper and magazine clippings, and files related to Herzog's research and activities with the American Academy for Religion and Comunidad Biblica Teologica Methodist Seminary. Series also contains materials relating to Black Studies and theology, the relationship between United Church of Christ (UCC) and the Evangelical Church of the Union in Germany (EKU). Various materials regarding Herzog's committee and faculty work at the university comprise a subseries.
The Writings and Speeches Series contains drafts and copies of Herzog's writings and speeches, primarily sermons from the 1950s. Including in this series are various manuscripts of Herzog's publications, including annotated bound manuscripts of The Gospel of Man.
Religion; Prayer; Liberty -- Religious aspects; Liberation theology; Durham (N.C.) -- History; African American churches; Black studies; Black theology; Civil disobedience -- Religious leaders; Civil rights movements -- North Carolina; College students -- United States -- History -- 20th century; College students -- United States -- Political activity -- History -- 20th century; College teachers -- Correspondence; College teachers -- United States; Human Rights -- Perú; Human Rights -- Religious aspects; Videotapes; Audiocassettes; Photographs; Scholars -- Correspondence; Theology -- Christian; Gutiérrez, Gustavo 1928-; Evangelische Kirche der Union; Herzog, Frederick -- Death; Duke University -- Faculty; Barth, Karl; Duke University. Divinity School; Duke University -- History; American Academy of Religion; Herzog, Frederick; United Church of Christ.General Synod; Herzog, Frederick
- Audiovisual Series, 1962-1999 and undated, 4 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  Contains two LP records of the Echoes of Evanston and sit-in songs, miscellaneous photographs, two reels of a debate panel on "God is Dead" and a Braswell interview. Cassette and VHS tapes comprise the bulk of this series. Cassettes are primarily of Herzog's class sessions and lectures, but also include a recording of a memorial service for Herzog in 1995 and a recording of a debate. VHS tapes are primarily of documentaries regarding churches in Peru, but also include interviews with Germans and other material on theology. More photographs relating to biographical information on Herzog can be found in the Biographical Series. This series is arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Braswell interview and thesis reel, 1973 Aug. 22 (Box 1)
    In preparation for the Febuary 18-22, 1974 continuing education seminar at Emory University.
  - Echoes of Evanston, produced by the World Council of Churches (LP Record), undated (Box 1)
  - Hildegard - ein Mensch vor Gott, 1984 (Audiotape) (Box 1)
    Includes two copies of a printed breakdown of the tape. Also see Course Materials Series.
  - Photos, undated (Box 1)
  - Sit-in Songs: Songs of the Freedom Riders, CORE (Congress of Racial Equality), 1962 (LP Record) (Box 1)
  - WBT-TV Panel, "God Is Dead - Pro and Con," 1966 (Reel) (Box 1)
  - VHS tapes, 8 tapes (Box 2)
    Includes commercial Spanish VHS tapes, documentaries about churches in Peru, interviews with Germans, tapes on theology, and a tape of a memorial service in Peru.
  - VHS tapes, 13 tapes (Box 3)
  - Cassette tapes, 1968-1995 (Box 4)
    Includes Christology, Theology, Mission Debate, Herzog courses, and memorial service tapes.
    - CT 200: Christology: The Person and Work of Christ, Fall 1991, 7 tapes (Box 4)
      Co-taught with Will Jennings.
    - CT 322: Nineteenth Century European Theology, Fall 1991, 18 tapes (Box 4)
    - Herzog, Frederick, "Toward a Waiting God," Duke Consultation, 1968 Apr. (Box 4)
    - Liberation Theology at the Turn of the Century: In Memory of Frederick Herzog, American Academy of Religion annual meeting, New Orleans, LA, 1996 Nov. 23-26, 2 tapes (Box 4)
    - A memorial service, 1995 Dec. 2 (Box 4)
    - Mission debate CBT, 1995 June, 2 tapes (Box 4)
    - Prayer and contemplation, undated (Box 4)
    - Rieger, Jörg seminar, sessions 1-2, Duke Divinity convocation, 1999, 3 tapes (Box 4)
- Biographical Series, 1944-2011 and undated, 2 boxes
  Primarily contains articles and items relating to Herzog's death and other miscellaneous biographical material. Also includes information regarding awards and certificates that Herzog received and miscellaneous photographs. Other photographs can be found in the Audiovisual Series. This series is arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Articles, etc. relating to Herzog's death, 1995-1996 (Box 5)
  - Ashley Reformed Parish, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Barth, Karl materials, 1947-1949 (Box 5)
  - General biographical material, 1944-2011, 3 folders (Box 5)
  - Humanitarian Award, 1990-1991 (Box 5)
  - Items relating to Herzog's death, 1995-1996 (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous biographical data, 1950-1995 (Box 5)
  - Photos, 1954-1993 and undated (Box 5)
  - Scholarship and admissions material, 1948-1949 (Box 6)
  - Trost, Frederick, "Reflections on Frederick Herzog and Public Welfare," 1996 Jan. (Box 6)
  - United States passport, visa, and citizenship, 1962-1963 (Box 6)
  - University certificates, 1946-1950 (Box 6)
- Correspondence Series, 1947-1995 and undated, 17 Boxes
  Contains correspondence to and from Frederick Herzog. Main language is English but a significant portion of the series is in German. The series begins with correspondence by individuals and groups with whom Herzog corresponded frequently, including correspondence with students and colleagues, presses, and various organizations; these are arranged alphabetically according to their last name. This is followed by a section of general correspondence arranged chronologically by year then alphabetically by last name. Significant correspondents include Brevard S. Childs, J.L. Mays, Eberhard Jüngel, Ernst Käsemann, Jürgen Moltmann, Gustavo Gutiérrez and James Cone.
  - American Academy of Religion (AAR) Liberation Theology Working Group, 1976-1985 (Box 7)
  - American Academy of Religion (AAR) Liberation Theology Working Group, round-robin regarding contextualization of theology, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - Amnesty International, 1982-1985 (Box 7)
  - Barth-Herzog, 1967-1976 (Box 7)
  - Bonn-Duke exchange, correspondence with Bernhard Unterkötter and Gerhard Sauter, 1980 and 1989 (Box 7)
  - Church World Service, 1949-1951 (Box 7)
  - Committee on Christian Responsibility and Cultural Trends, 1962-1968 (Box 7)
  - Copy of letter from Karl Barth to Karl Jaspers, sent to Fred Herzog, 1953 (Box 7)
  - Cushman, Robert, 1967-1980, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Detroit 1975 Theology in the Americas conference (Box 7)
  - Divinity School, Sabbatical, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
  - Divinity School's integration: Herzog's Call to Duke, 1959 (Box 7)
  - Draft letter (German), 1949 (Box 7)
  - Duke colleagues, 1957-1995 (Box 7)
  - Duke Memos/Newsletters, 1965-1969 (Box 7)
  - Edwards, William, 1960-1989, 1 of 2 (Box 7)
  - Edwards, William, 1960-1989, 2 of 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Evangelische Kommentare, 1971-1995, 6 of 7 (Box 8)
  - Evangelische Kommentare, 1971-1995, 7 of 7 folders (Box 9)
  - Evangelische Kommentare (Edition at Large), 1978-1994 (Box 9)
  - Fan mail, 1961-1994 (Box 9)
  - The Future of Hope, 1969-1970 (Box 9)
  - General, 1956-1995, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Get-well mail, 1995 Sep. (Box 9)
  - Gutiérrez, Gustavo, 1984 (Box 9)
  - Gutierrez, Gustavo, 1995 Jan. 17 (Box 9)
  - Herzog to Judith Ruderman, 1995 (Box 10)
    Shortly before Frederick's passing.
  - Herzog-Karl Barth correspondence, 1947-1954 (Box 10)
  - Herzog's 60th Birthday, 1985 (Box 10)
  - India invitation, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Interpretation, with, 1975-1977 (Box 10)
  - Karwehl, Richard, 1964-1973 (Box 10)
    Fred Herzog's father-in-law.
  - Knight, Douglas, 1968-1969 (Box 10)
  - Langford, Thomas, 1980 and undated (Box 10)
  - Lile, David: exchange student in Bonn and Lima, 1986-1990d (Box 10)
  - Local 77, 1966 (Box 10)
  - Moltmann/Jüngel, 1970s (Box 10)
  - Moltmann, Jürgen, 1957-1995, 4 folders (Box 10)
    Includes articles.
  - North Dakota ordination issues, 1950-1959 (Box 11)
  - Orbis Books, 1987-1995 (Box 11)
  - Peace discussions between churches in the USA, Western Germany and East Germany, 1981 and undated (Box 11)
  - Peru correspondence, 1988-1995, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Peru correspondence before May 1991 trip (with 3 divinity school colleagues) (Box 11)
  - Relating to Herzog's publications, 1966-1991 (Box 11)
  - Sabbatical, Tübingen, 1971-1972 (Box 11)
  - Schrage, Wolfgang 1984-1985 (Box 11)
  - Scribner's on Understanding God, 1965-1966 (Box 11)
  - Seabury Press and Jim Cone, 1972-1974 (Box 11)
  - Sit-in, 1964-1965 (Box 11)
  - Student recommendations, 1970 and 1994 (Box 11)
  - Students, 1971-1995 (Box 11)
  - Task Force of Professional Theologians regarding contextualization of North American theology, 1973-1977 (Box 11)
  - Theology and Public Policy Program at Duke, 1968-1975 (Box 12)
  - Theology in the Americas, 1976-1977 (Box 12)
  - Trost, Frederick letters, 1987-1988 (Box 12)
  - Unidentified correspondence, 1961-1975 (Box 12)
  - Weth, Rudolf, 1988-1990 (Box 12)
  - Wethington, Mark, 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Briefe, 1947 Nov.-1948 Aug., 2 folders (Box 12)
  - 1949-1951 (Box 12)
  - 1953 (including Markus Barth) (Box 12)
  - Letters, 1954-1957, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Letters, 1960-1962, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - 1962 (Box 13)
  - 1963 (Box 13)
  - 1964, 3 folders (Box 13)
  - 1965, 1 of 2 (Box 13)
  - 1965, 2 of 2 folders (Box 14)
  - 1965-1967, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - 1966 (Box 14)
  - 1967 (Box 14)
  - 1968, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - 1969, 4 folders (Box 14)
  - 1970, 1 of 5 (Box 14)
  - 1970, 2-5 of 5 folders (Box 15)
  - 1971, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - 1972, 1 of 3 (Box 15)
  - 1972, 2-3 of 3 folders (Box 16)
  - 1973, 4 folders (Box 16)
  - 1974, 4 folders (Box 16)
  - 1975, 3 folders (Box 17)
  - 1976 (Box 17)
  - 1977 (Box 17)
  - 1978 (Box 17)
  - 1979 (Box 17)
  - 1970s, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - 1979-1981 (Box 17)
  - Letters, mostly 1983-1984, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - 1983-1985, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - 1985-1986, 2 of 4 (Box 18)
  - 1985-1986, 3-4 of 4 folders (Box 19)
  - 1985-1989 (Box 19)
  - 1986-1987, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Summer 1987 (Box 19)
  - Letters, 1987-1988, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - 1988-1989 (Box 19)
  - 1980s (Box 19)
  - 1990-1991 (Box 19)
  - Summer 1991 (Box 20)
  - Letters, 1991-1995 (mostly 1993-1995), 2 folders (Box 20)
  - 1957-1960, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - 1962-1964, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - 1976-1977, 1 of 2 (Box 21)
  - 1976-1977, 2 of 2 folders (Box 22)
  - 1977-1978, 2 folders (Box 22)
  - 1981-1983, 3 folders (Box 22)
  - 1983-1984, 2 folders (Box 23)
- Course Materials Series, 1953-1995 and undated, 9 boxes
  Contains material related to Herzog's religion and divinity courses. Also contains material on Duke student exchange program with the University of Bonn and the Peru and Bolivia student exchange program. This series is arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Bonn Exchange, 1974-1984, 6 folders (Box 24)
  - CBT Teaching, Lima, 1992 Fall (Box 24)
  - Christian Theology, C.T. 32.2, Fall Semester, 1972 (Box 24)
  - Christian Theology, C.T. 32.2, Fall Semester, 1974 (Box 24)
  - Christian Theology, 1979, 1 of 2 (Box 24)
  - Christian Theology, 1979, 2 of 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Christian Theology, Spring 1991 (Box 25)
  - Christian Theology and Conquest, Democracy, and the Role of Religion, 1992-1993 (Box 25)
  - Christian Theology and Theology of Paul Tillich, Spring 1991 (Box 25)
  - Church and Sacraments and Prayer and Contemplation in the Modern Church, Fall 1989-1990 (Box 25)
  - Class evaluations, 1975-1982 (Box 25)
  - Class work, including student writing, 1993-1995 (Box 25)
  - Collection of texts and images from Peru by David Lile, exchange student from Duke, 1989 (Box 25)
  - Conquest, Democracy in Latin Ameirica and Person and Work of Christ, 1994 (Box 25)
  - Co-teaching in Bonn on Eucharist, 1990; report on the consultation process, 1988-1989 (Box 25)
  - Course evaluations, 1980-1992 (Box 26)
  - Coursework, 1964-1995 and undated (Box 26)
  - Coursework (syllabi, etc.), 1964-1995 and undated (Box 26)
  - Coursework in Germany (Bonn), 1979-1990 (Box 26)
  - Coursework in Germany (Tübingen), 1972 (Box 26)
  - Coursework in Germany, 1988 (Box 26)
  - Coursework with Moltmann, Tübingen, 1970-1972 (Box 26)
  - Covenant Discipleship Quarterly and documents, 1986-1987 (Box 27)
  - Duke Bonn II Consultation, 1984 (Box 27)
  - Duke-Bonn, 1977-1995 and undated, 4 of 7 (Box 27)
  - Duke-Bonn, 1977-1995 and undated, 5-7 of 7 folders (Box 28)
  - God and the Human Being and Church and Sacraments, 1990 (Box 28)
  - Illuminations of Hildegard of Bingen, 1985 (Box 28)
    Note: Herzog repeatedly taught the theoogy of Hildegard of Bingen. Contains annotations and notes. Also see Audiovisual Series.
  - Introduction to Christian Theology and the Church and Social Change, 1978-1979, 2 folders (Box 28)
  - Material for teaching the Columbus Anniversary, 1992, 1 of 2 (Box 28)
  - Material for teaching the Columbus Anniversary, 1992, 2 of 2 folders (Box 29)
  - Miscellaneous course information, 1980-1982 (Box 29)
  - Miscellaneous course information, 1987-1995 (Box 29)
  - Mission House Theological Seminary catalogue, 1953-1958 (Box 29)
  - The Nature and Mission of the Church and Twentieth Century European Theology, Spring 1977 (Box 29)
  - Nineteenth-Century European Theology, 1987; Church and Sacraments, 1987; Systematic Theology, 1988 (Box 29)
  - Nineteenth-Century European Theology, Fall 1989 (Box 29)
  - Notes/Texts relating to Kitty Dixon's tapes, 1991 (Box 30)
  - The Person and Work of Christ, nineteenth-century European theology, church and society in contemporary Latin America, 1991 (Box 30)
  - The Person and Work of Christ, student papers on feminist issues, 1990 (Box 30)
  - Peru and Bolivia student exchange, 1988-1995 (Box 30)
  - Philosophical Method in Religious Studies and Conquest, Democracy, and Religion in Latin America, 1993 (Box 30)
  - Prayer and Contemplation, 1986 (1989) (Box 30)
  - Prayer and Contemplation, Christian Theology, Philosophical Theology, 1987 (Box 30)
  - Prayer and Contemplation course material, Fall 1995 (Box 31)
  - Prayer and Contemplation, The Person and Work of Christ, field education seminar, 1988 (Box 31)
  - Seminar: Funktions wandel der Dogmatik, Bonn, 1978 (Box 31)
  - Student evaluations, 1980 (Box 31)
  - Student papers on feminist theology (Barth, Tillich, etc.), 1990 (Box 31)
  - Student papers on feminist topics, 1990 (Box 31)
  - Syllabi, 1964-1975 (Box 31)
  - Teaching American liberation theology in Germany, Wuppertal, 1988 (Box 31)
  - Teaching on Latin America, 1988 (Box 31)
  - Teaching at Tübingen University, 1972 (Box 32)
  - Universität Basel kollegeinbuch fürden zuhörer, 1947 (Box 32)
  - 1975-1976 (Box 32)
  - 1984 (Box 32)
  - 1988 (Box 32)
- Notebooks Series, 1962-1984 and undated, 3 Boxes
  Contains notebooks of student-kept logs of course sessions taught by Frederick Herzog and notebooks in which Herzog kept notes and writings related to his publications and his teaching. Notebooks are ordered chronologically.
  - Untitled, undated (Box 33)
  - Class Logs Subseries, 1962-1974
    Student-kept logs of course sessions taught by Frederick Herzog. Courses focused on such topics as Friedrich Schleiermacher, Paul Tillich, 20th-century European theology and the doctrine of God. Notebooks ordered chronologically.
    - Schleiermacher and Tillich Seminar, 1962 Feb. 7-1962 May 16 (Box 33)
    - Schleiermacher Seminar, 1964 Spring (Box 33)
    - Contemporary European Theology, 1965 (Box 33)
    - C.T. 320: [Schleiermacher Seminar?], 1966 Spring (Box 33)
    - Doctrine of God, 1968 Spring (Box 33)
      Course was co-taught by Herzog and Jürgen Moltmann.
    - C.T. 328: 20th Century European Theology, 1972 Fall (Box 33)
    - C.T. 322: [Schleiermacher and Barth?], 1974 Fall (Box 33)
  - Class Lectures Subseries,1968-1984 and undated
    Lectures on such topics as black power and black religion, 20th century European theology, systematic theology and the nature and mission of the Church. Lecture notebooks are ordered chronologically.
    - God Waiting on Man, [1966?] (Box 33)
    - Systematic Theology, 1968 Fall (Box 33)
    - C.T. 100: Black Power and Black Religion, [1970?] (Box 34)
    - C.T. 300: Systematic Theology, 1970 (Box 34)
    - C.T. 32.2: Introduction to Christian Theology, 1972 Fall, 2 notebooks (Box 34)
    - C.T. 328: 20th Century European Theology, 1972 Fall (Box 34)
    - C.T. 32.2: Christian Theology, 1973 Fall (Box 34)
    - C.T. 300: Systematic Theology, 1973 Spring (Box 34)
    - C.T. 32.2: Introduction to Christian Theology, 1974 Fall (Box 34)
    - Person and Work of Christ, Spring 1974 (Box 35)
    - C.T. 215: The Nature and Mission of the Church, 1976 Spring, 2 notebooks (Box 35)
    - Theology and church policy, Spring 1978 (Box 35)
    - [Introduction to Christian Theology?], 1984 Mar. 16 - 1984 Nov. 29 (Box 35)
    - C.T. 119: Prayer and Contemplation, 1989 Fall (Box 35)
    - C.T. 300: Systematic Theology 11A, undated (Box 35)
    - C.T. 300: Systematic Theology 11B, undated (Box 35)
    - C.T. 303: [Political Theology?], undated (Box 35)
    - Untitled, 1983 (Box 35)
    - Untitled, 1983-1984 (Box 35)
- Research Files Series, 1947-2005 and undated (bulk 1960-1995), 37 Boxes